Guide to the Toba Pato Tucker Photographs and Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Re Viewing the American Landscape West & Southwest, 2012-2015; Series V; (29 boxes)
  - Portfolio #4
    - Inkjet prints, 17 inches by 22 inches
      - Misty Fjords, Behm Canal
        - Untitled (No. 7165), 2015 (Box 282 (Oversize), Folder 3987)
        - Untitled (No. 7177), 2015 (Box 282 (Oversize), Folder 3988)
        - Untitled (No. 7186), 2015 (Box 282 (Oversize), Folder 3989)
        - Untitled (No. 7188), 2015 (Box 282 (Oversize), Folder 3990)
        - Interleaving sheets
    - Reference Inkjet Prints, 8.5 inches by 11 inches
      Organized under two headings: Portraits of Turcker and Photographs of the Inland Passage by Others.
      - Portraits of Tucker
        - Toba Pato Tucker, Photographer - Glacier Bay National Park, Alaska, 2015 (Box 283, Folder 3991-3992)
          Photographs by unidentified photographers
      - Photographs of the Inland Passage by Others
        - Main street of Sitka, Alaska (No. 368), printed 2015; image created circa 1897 (Box 283, Folder 3993)
          Photograph by Winter & Pond. Original print in Winter & Pond, Photographs of the Yukon and Klondike, Alaska, Call number WA Photos 131. Image provided reference for Tucker's Image No. 2309, 2313, and 2335.
        - Sitka, Alaska, printed 2015; image created circa 1881 (Box 283, Folder 3994)
          Title from manuscript inscription. Photograph by Richard Maynard. Original print in Richard Maynard, Photographs of Alaska and British Columbia, Call number WA Photos 62. Image provided reference for Tucker's Image No. 2309, 2313, and 2335.
        - Untitled, printed 2015; image created circa 1881 (Box 283, Folder 3995)
          View of Sitka, Alaska. Photograph by Richard Maynard. Original print in Richard Maynard, Photographs of Alaska and British Columbia, Call number WA Photos 62. Image provided reference for Tucker's Image No. 2309, 2313, and 2335.
        - Untitled, printed 2015; image created circa 1881 (Box 283, Folder 3996)
          View of a steamboat at Sitka, Alaska. Photograph by Richard Maynard. Original print in Richard Maynard, Photographs of Alaska and British Columbia, Call number WA Photos 62. Image provided reference for Tucker's Image No. 2309, 2313, and 2335.
        - Untitled, printed 2015; image created circa 1881 (Box 283, Folder 3997)
        - Untitled, printed 2015; image created circa 1881 (Box 283, Folder 3998)
          View of Sitka, Alaska, of Lincoln Street toward St. Michael the Archangel Cathedral. Photograph by Richard Maynard. Original print in Richard Maynard, Photographs of Alaska and British Columbia, Call number WA Photos 62. Image provided reference for Tucker's Image No. 2309, 2313, and 2335.
        - Seaward from Sitka, Alaska (No. 1123), printed 2015; image created circa 1892 (Box 283, Folder 3999)
          Photograph by Frank La Roche. Original print in Frank La Roche, Photographs of Alaska, Call number WA Photos 98. Image provided reference for Tucker's Image No. 2309, 2313, and 2335.
        - Sitka, Alaska (No. 1124), printed 2015; image created circa 1892 (Box 283, Folder 4000)
        - Untitled, printed 2015; image created circa 1931 (Box 283, Folder 4001)
          View of a sea plane flying low over water in Alaska. Original print in Bernard Rosecrans Hubbard, Photographs of Alaska, Call number WA Photos 295. Image provided reference for Tucker's Image No. 7150.
        - Section of Muir Glacier, Alaska (No. 1171), printed 2015; image created circa 1892 (Box 283, Folder 4002)
          Photograph by Frank La Roche. Original print in Frank La Roche, Photographs of Alaska, Call number WA Photos 98. Image provided reference for Tucker's images of glaciers.
        - Takou Glacier, Alaska (No. 1183), printed 2015; image created circa 1892 (Box 283, Folder 4003)
          View of the Taku Glacier. Photograph by Frank La Roche. Original print in Frank La Roche, Photographs of Alaska, Call number WA Photos 98. Image provided reference for Tucker's images of glaciers.
        - Section of Muir Glacier, Alaska. Reflected (No. 1173), printed 2015; image created circa 1892 (Box 283, Folder 4004)
        - Profile of Muir Glacier, Alaska (No. 139) and A Floating Iceberg, in Glacier Bay, Alaska (No. 227), printed 2015; image created circa 1892 (Box 283, Folder 4005)
          Photographs by Frank La Roche. Original prints in Frank La Roche, Photographs of Alaska, Call number WA Photos 98. Image provided reference for Tucker's images of glaciers.
        - Untitled and Steamer Queen in Ice, Takou Inlet, Alaska (No. 240), printed 2015; image created circa 1892 (Box 283, Folder 4006)
          Views of the Steamer Queen and Taku Inlet. Photograph by Frank La Roche. Original print in Frank La Roche, Photographs of Alaska, Call number WA Photos 98. Images provided reference for Tucker's Image No. 6679 and 7055.
        - Steamer Queen in Ice, Takou Inlet, Alaska, printed 2015; image created circa 1898 (Box 283, Folder 4007)
          View of the Steamer Queen and Taku Inlet. Photograph by Frank La Roche. Published in Frank La Roche, En Route to the Klondike (Chicago: W.B. Conkey Company, 1898). Image provided reference for Tucker's Image No. 6679 and 7055.
        - Steamer Queen in Ice, Glacier Bay, printed 2015; image created 1891 June (Box 283, Folder 4008)
          Photograph by L. Woodull. Original print in L. Woodull, Photograph Album of Alaska and the Pacific Coast, Call number WA Photos 40. Image provided reference for Tucker's Image No. 6679 and 7055.
        - Glacier, at Takou, From Ice Floe (No. 30), printed 2015; image created circa 1881 (Box 283, Folder 4009)
          View of the Taku Inlet. Photograph by Richard Maynard. Original print in Richard Maynard, Photographs of Alaska and British Columbia, Call number WA Photos 62. Image provided reference for Tucker's images of glaciers.
        - Fort Wrangle, Alaska (Image No. 454), printed 2015; image created circa 1897 (Box 283, Folder 4010)
          Bird's-eye view of town and harbor of Wrangell, Alaska. Photograph by Frank La Roche. The object identification number referenced on print does not link to a digital surrogate of the image at the Beinecke Rare Book & Manuscript Library. From a digital surrogate created by the University of Washington Libraries, Special Collections, and made available through Wikipedia. Original print in Frank La Roche Photographs, University of Washington Libraries, Special Collections. Image provided reference for Tucker's Image No. 6679 and 7055.
        - Lamplugh Glacier, Alaska, printed 2015; 1941 August 28 (Box 283, Folder 4011)
          Photograph by William Osgood Field. From a digital surrogate created by the National Snow and Ice Data Center, and made available through Alaska Channel. Original print in the Glacier Photograph Collection, National Snow and Ice Data Center. Image provided reference for Tucker's Image No. 6608-6698.
        - Muir Glacier, Alaska (No. C141), printed 2015; circa 1895 (Box 283, Folder 4012)
          Photograph by Winter & Pond. From a digital surrogate created by the United States Geological Survey. Original postcard in a private collection. Image provided reference for Tucker's Image No. 6539-6648.
        - Muir Inlet, Alaska (No. 7807), printed 2015; circa 1890 (Box 283, Folder 4013)
          Photograph by G. D. Hazard. From a digital surrogate created by the United States Geological Survey. Original print in Glacier Bay National Park and Preserve Archive. Image provided reference for Tucker's Image No. 6539-6648.